爸爸
Dad?
操
Fuck.
他们说你死了  卡萨姆把你杀了
They told me that you were dead, that Qassem killed you.
李奥  到底是怎么回事
Leo, what the fuck is going on?
我这下算是明白了
I've got a fair idea.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你爸爸伪造了自己被枪毙的录像
Your dad faked his own execution.
没错  他一直把我们耍的团团转
Yeah. He played us all along.
艾斯特  你爸爸是恐怖分子
Ester, your father is a terrorist.
迈克
Mike.
他跟个想要害死千万人的坏蛋沆瀣一气
He works for a man who wants to kill thousands of people.
他们撒谎  艾斯特
They're lying to you, Ester.
艾斯特  这虽然看似荒唐  但我们没骗你
Ester, I know it looks bad, but I didn't lie to you.
我就站在你面前  不是吗
I'm here, aren't I,
而且卡萨姆为什么要杀我
and why would Qassem want to kill me?
去吧  跟卡萨姆到车里去
Go on. You go with Qassem to the car,
我马上就到
and I'll be right behind you.
艾斯特  等等
Ester! Hey!
你骗我
You lied to me!
你说他死了
You told me that he was dead!
你为什么说谎
Why would you say that?
他带你出去是因为不想让你目睹
He's taking you outside because he doesn't want you
他杀我们的场景
to see him kill us.
当然不是
That's not true.
我不会伤害他们的  我保证
I am not going to hurt them, i promise.
去吧  跟卡萨姆到车里去
Go on. Go with Qassem to the car.
-走吧艾斯特  -别磨蹭了
- Come on, Ester. It's OK. - Go on now.
算你狠
Well played.
你这人还真是守信  是吧
You got a good track record with your promises, don't you?
带她上车
Get her to the car.
你们总是阴魂不散
You just won't go away.
是啊  还真被道尔顿说准了
Yeah. Dalton was right about you.
你们低估了她的能力  我可没有
You underestimated her. I didn't.
所以你就把她害死了?
Ha! So you had her killed?
我们既搞定了本拉登
We got Bin Laden.
朱海瑞也自然不在话下  你这混帐东西
We'll get Al-Zuhari, you piece of shit.
你们这些冷血的人
You fucking people!
对自己人的伤亡算的一清二楚
You count every one of your dead servicemen,
却对其余受害者的死伤不闻不问
but you pay no attention to the body count of your victims.
你们不在乎  他们不要紧
You don't care. They're not important.
朱海瑞六个月前就已经死了
Al-Zuhari's been dead for 6 months,
在以色列对叙利亚的一次空袭中丧生
killed in an Israeli air strike in Syria.
带他们去见乌尔诺夫
Deliver these men to Ulyanov.
他自会处理
He will dispose of them.
这日子还能更糟糕点吗
Can this day get any worse?
你觉得乌尔诺夫会直接杀掉他们吗  长官
You think Ulyanov will kill them straightaway, sir?
不  估计他们没那么走运
No. I don't think they'll be that lucky.
醒着吗?
嗯
我三点方向有两个
我们为什么不直接把他们干掉?
Why can't we just kill them ourselves?
你六点方向有一个  有武器
卡马里跟俄罗斯人谈好了
Kamali has a deal with the Russians.
他们想亲自动手
They want to do it themselves.
数三下
数三下?
还是直接上?
让你数就数!
一...  二...  三
什么
What?
你还活着吗
You alive?
当然
Yeah!
操  该死
Fuck! Shit!
那赶紧把我解开
Then cut me free!
趴下  趴下
Get down, down, down!
我有办法了
I've got an idea.
天呐  阿迈
Jesus Christ, Mikey!
我比你更需要这辆车
I need this car a lot more than you do.
快点
Come on!
再见  混蛋
See you, fuckers!
快进来
Yeah. Get in.
谢谢你  感谢你搭乘本车
Cheers. Nice of you to drop in.
好吧  我们得抓个活的
All right. We got to get a live one.
快他妈靠边停车
Fucking pull over right now!
说"请"
Say, "Please."
"请你"快他妈靠边停车
Please fucking pull over!
妈的  迈克
Fuck! Mike!
该死  我看到了  看到了
Shit. Yeah. I see it, I see it.
人家修路呢  伙计
Construction, dude!
我们开不过去了
We're not gonna make that.
操  该死
Oh, shit!
我已经在打方向了
I'm doing it!
你是傻逼  知道吗
You're an idiot, you know!
坚持住  你这狗娘养的
Hold on, you motherfucker!
天呐
Aw, man!
他妈的  真该死
Oh, shit! Fuck me!
我都说了你过不去
I told you you wouldn't make it.
我刚救了你一命  [你都没句谢谢?]
I just saved your arse!
可我们翻车了  迈克尔
We're upside down, Michael!
那边有个活的
We've got a live one over there.
操  活的?
Fuck! A live one?
我们先出去再说
Let's get out of here.
过来  你这混蛋
Come here, you fucker!
以慈悲的真主之名
In the name of Allah the gracious,
你们将自己献给了真主及其伟大事业
you have offered yourself to Allah and his cause--
拥护正义  争取我们保卫自己
justice, the right to defend ourselves...
免遭帝国主义压迫的权利
against imperialist oppressors.
他们没去乌尔诺夫那里
They never arrived at Ulyanov's.
我祈祷真主...
I pray that Allah...
20号分部依然是个威胁
Twenty are still out there.
我们现在就行动
Let's move now.
够了  够了
Enough, enough!
我们没时间了
We haven't time.
-让他们准备好  -神父  走吧
- Get them ready. - Allah. Let's go.
快点  快点
Come on! Come on!
去年五月  以色列对叙利亚实施了一次空袭
There was an Israeli strike on a Syrian target last May.
从那之后就没人再见过朱海瑞
Since then, there have been no confirmed sightings of Al-Zuhari
除了我们在布达佩斯得到的视频
except for the video that we retrieved in Budapest.
那也可能是预先录好的  是卡马里使的障眼法
Which could have been prerecorded and planted by Kamali.
我们到底错在什么地方
Where the fuck did we go wrong?
卡马里开枪杀了巴克斯特
Kamali shot Baxter,
害死了道尔顿
had Dalton killed.
马丁内斯因为他进了医院
Martinez is in the hospital because of him.
他利用我们得到病毒
He used us to get to the virus
还他妈要把我们交给乌尔诺夫
and fucking handed us off to Ulyanov.
告诉我  我们为什么一错再错
So you tell me how the fuck did we get here?
喂  你也跟大家一样中了他的圈套
Whoa. You bought into this as much as any of us, mate.
卧底英雄卡马里
The hero Kamali leading the undercover life
还有中情局那套狗屁...
and all that CIA bullshit you--
闭嘴  迈克尔
Shut the fuck up, Michael.
-你说什么  -为什么一错再错
- Excuse me? - How did this happen?
-告诉我真相  -你说什么?
- Tell me the truth. - What?
为什么一错再错
How the fuck did this happen?
真相就是
The truth is
道尔顿曾警告过你  但你选择相信卡马里
that Dalton warned you about this, and you chose Kamali's side.
-是吗  -没错
- Did I? - Yeah, really.
这就是你的想法吗  迈克尔
That's what you think, Michael
-我就是这么想的  斯科特  -真的假的
- Yeah, it is what I fucking think, Scott.  - Really?
你怎么想关我屁事
I don't give a fuck what you think!
够了  够了
That's enough, that's enough!
你少管我们
Stay the fuck out of this!
你他妈有什么毛病
What the fuck is your problem?
我说够了
I said enough!
抱歉
Sorry.
你们说的没错  责任在我
No. You're right. The buck does stop with me,
但卡马里利用了我们所有人
but Kamali used us all.
他利用了中情局  利用了我
He used the CIA, he used me,
也利用了你  斯科特  利用了大家
and he used you, Scott, everyone,
所以我们为何不集中精力阻止他呢
so why don't we concentrate on stopping him?
你们终于给我带回来一个活的
So you finally managed to bring me a live one.
给我撬开他的嘴
Well, you get something out of him,
不惜一切代价
whatever it takes.
是
Yes, boss.
特务身份查的怎么样了
How we doing on the clean skins' IDs?
他们使用了快速修补算法
They're using a fast in-painting algorithm.
谢谢你  中士
Uh, thank you, sergeant.
能尽快查出来吗
Could you just do it as quickly as possible?
我们需要查明身份
We need those identities.
阿迈  上面发生的事怪我不好
Sorry about up there, Mikey.
或许是有点...
Might have been a bit--
是吗  "有点"?
Yeah. A bit?
好吧  不止一点
All right. More than a bit.
嗯  我不应该...
Yeah. I shouldn't have, uh--
你确实不应该
No. You probably shouldn't have.
好吧
Ok.
真不敢相信道尔顿那个疯婆子竟然说对了
I can't believe that crazy bitch Dalton was right.
他把我们都给耍了
Well, he had us all fooled.
你确定自己准备好了吗
Sure you're ready for this?
不确定  你呢?
No. You?
这种事我们要是不干
People like you and me don't do shit like this,
那还能交给谁呢
where's that leave everyone else, huh?
我不怕死
I'm not afraid to die!
你死不了
You're not gonna die.
卡马里的目标是什么
What's Kamali's target?
这是你们进入空军基地的证件
These are you identities for the air base.
每个分队都有自己的目标
Each cell has its own target,
但所有人的目标是一致的
but everyone serves the same goal.
其他都不重要
Nothing else matters.
我们潜入基地  释放病毒  然后离开
We go in, we release the virus, and then we leave.
死神就会追随着那些士兵
These soldiers will carry death.
我们中间有些人可能看不到明天的太阳
Some of us may not live to see the end of this day.
要做好牺牲的准备
Be prepared to make that sacrifice,
柏林东南部
发现乌尔诺夫了吗
Do you have eyes on Ulyanov?
是
I do.
就位吧  我马上就到
Get in position. I'll be there shortly.
-那是什么  -没关系的
- What is that? - It's fine.
-不  爸爸  -必须注射  艾斯特
- No, Dad, no. - I have to do this, Ester.
这是预防措施
It's protection.
很快就好了
I'll be quick.
进去  出来
In and...out.
好了  完成
Done. Finished.
良药苦口
Good because it hurt.
他们被带去哪儿了
Where were they taken?
说呀
Well?
迈克尔和达米恩不是你想象中的那种人
Michael and Damien are not who you think they are.
他们不是你的朋友
They're not your friends.
他们是敌人
They are the enemy.
他们救过我的命
They saved my life.
艾斯特  他们认为
Ester, they believe that
他们做的是正确的
what they're doing is right.
他们觉得自己是好人
They think they're good men.
他们错了  他们是侩子手  杀人犯
They're not. They are killers, murderers.
不  他们不是
No, they're not.
艾斯特
Ester...
那个杀害你母亲的飞行员
the pilot who killed your mother,
他无缘无故的向救护车开枪
who fired indiscriminately on an ambulance
而那辆救护车里正好载着
that was carrying her to hospital,
刚把你生出来的她
having just given birth to you,
那个飞行员也觉得自己是个好人
that pilot thought he was a good man, too.
这曾属于你的母亲
This belonged to your mother,
那位你从未见过的女人
the woman you never met.
你打算杀了他们
You're gonna kill them...
对不对
aren't you?
我们有权利生活在一个
We have the right to live in a world
人们彼此相爱的世界上
where people like us,
如此  我们爱的人才会安全  艾斯特
and those we love are safe, Ester.
站住
Stop.
我是菲利普·洛克
Philip Locke...
20号分部的人
Section Twenty.
你来这做什么
Why are you here?
卡马里低估了我的手下
Kamali underestimated my people.
他以为可以轻松的带他们去见你
He thought he could simply deliver them to you.
我希望你不要再犯同样的错误
I want to see you don't make the same mistake.
你选错了生意伙伴  乌尔诺夫先生
You chose the wrong business partner, Mr. Ulyanov.
这不是生意
This is not business.
这是私人恩怨
It's personal.
你的人杀害了我的儿子
Your men murdered my son.
是啊  可怜的维克多
Yeah. Poor, old Viktor.
他在错误的时间出现在了错误的地点
He was in the wrong place at the wrong time.
错误的地点
Wrong place?
你根本无发理解失去孩子的痛楚
You have no idea. To lose a child.
恰恰相反  我很理解
Oh, yes, I do.
我也有一个被人谋害的儿子
I also had a son who was murdered,
而他只是个无辜的学生
but he was an innocent school boy
他唯一的错误是他成了我的孩子
whose only fault was to be my child,
而不是某个觊觎他父亲地位的瘾君子
not a coke-snorting prick with eyes on his father's throne.
-操  -别轻举妄动
- Fuck-- - Be very careful.
好吧
Ok.
直说你的来意吧
Say what you have to say.
无论卡马里成败与否  一旦这事结束了
Whether Kamali succeeds or fails, once this is done,
将会有一场前所未见的通缉追捕行动
there will be a hunt the likes of which has never been seen.
如果李奥·卡马里成功了
If Leo Kamali succeeds,
这个世界将会发生巨大的改变
the world is gonna be very, very different.
但仍然会有像我这样的人
But there will still be people like me
去寻找那些同谋者
looking for those who help them,
而你将会排在名单的第一位
and you will be top of that list.
你现在帮助我的话
You help us now,
我保证你不会出现在那名单上
you have my word you won't be on that list.
行  我可以交出你想要的东西
OK. I'll give you what you want,
但你明白代价是什么
but you know the price.
你们问出什么了吗
What did you get?
计划是先感染服役人员
Well... the plan is to infect servicemen
让他们在回家前成为病毒携带者
with the virus before they go home.
那些携带者会让疾病在美国蔓延
Those carriers will spread the disease in America.
地点呢
Where?
拉姆斯坦因空军基地
Ramstein Air Base.
据说他们已经在那儿了
He says they're already there.
姓名  身份信息呢
Names, IDs.
他说他只知道这些情况
Claims that's all he knows.
马丁内斯正在拉姆斯坦因基地  等着被送回来
Martinez is at Ramstein, waiting to be sent home.
我们会确保让她获悉此次行动
We'll make sure she's kept in the loop.
带上装备  瑞姆跟我走
Kit up. I'll bring Richmond.
她正在破解特务的身份
She's IDing the clean skins.
-你们也来  -是长官
- You two, follow. - Sir.
美国空军  拉姆斯坦因基地
早安
Morning.
等等  请把证件放在扫描仪上
Hold on. Put your I.D. on the scanner, please.
-谢谢  -谢谢
- Thank you. - Thank you.
你想让我依据一次审问而关闭整个基地
You want me to close down a base because of one interrogation?
是的  将军  我需要你停飞所有飞机
Yes, general. I want you to ground the aircraft
并封锁这个基地
and seal off this base.
这里的安保工作是全世界最彻底的
Security here is better than anywhere else in the world.
长官  他们会躲过系统的检查
Sir, they'll be invisible to the system,
但根据我们的情报  他们的人已经混进去了
but we have intel that says these people are already here.
你们的安全系统已经遭到破坏
Your security's been breached.
我严重怀疑你们情报的准确性  洛克上校
I seriously doubt the quality of your intel, Colonel Locke.
每个人都会经过审核与检查
Everyone is vetted and checked,
身份证件与生物识别双保险
identity cards, biometrics.
这些人不可能大摇大摆的
There is no way these people can just walk
进入美国空军基地
right into an American air base.
洛克上校
Colonel Locke.
金  拉姆斯坦因是卡马里的目标
Kim, Ramstein is Kamali's target.
他打算感染返家的伤员
He's planning to infect the wounded on the way home.
特务们已携带病毒潜入进去了
The clean skins are coming in with the virus.
提高警惕  我们已经在来的路上了
Just hang tight. We're on our way now.
一旦瑞姆拿到照片  她会全部传过去给你
When Richmond gets photos, she'll send them through.
收到
Copy that.
上校  我找到他们了
Colonel, I have them.
有多少人
How many?
目前有14名  但可能会有更多
So far, we have 14, but there's likely to be more.
-将军  -上校
- Brigadier general. - Colonel.
这是我们目前发现的人
Well, this is what we've got.
这14个人拥有进入基地所需的身份证件
These 14 have IDs for the base.
也许还有更多
There may be more.
我不能冒这个风险
I'm not taking any chances.
上尉  马上封锁整个空军基地
Captain, I want you to lock down the entire air base.
停飞所有航班  不准任何人进出
Ground all aircraft. No one in or out.
-收到  -是  长官
- Sir. - Yes, sir.
格雷中尉跟我来
Lieutenant Greg, on me.
我们得马上把这些照片放到网上
We need to get these pictures online immediately.
中士  这是我的首席安全顾问
Sergeant, my head of security.
让他把这些身份信息录入系统
Let him put those IDs into the system.
-是  -别担心
- Sir. - Don't worry.
两分钟后  每个人都会知道这些人的真面目
Two minutes, everyone will know who these guys are.
B1和B2已抵达医疗中心
Bravo One and Two at medical center.
请把证件放到扫描仪上
Can you put your I.D. on the scanner, please?
好的  当然
Yeah, sure.
打扰下  我们是英国部队的
Excuse me. British military.
你们的人在等我们
you're expecting us.
我们要和你们的指挥官对话
We need to talk to your commanding officer.
这边走
This way.
他是其中一员  身份已确认
He's one of them. Positive I.D.!
重复  他是一名入侵者
Repeat! He's an intruder!
后退  我让你后退
Step back. I said step back.
迈克
Mike!
-该死  -立即戒严此区域
- Shit! - Clear the area now!
安全
Clear!
我们放倒了三名特务
We got 3 clean skins down,
他们都穿着空军维修队的制服
all dressed as Air Force maintenance.
他们用箱子装着东西带进来了
They were bringing something through in a case.
把图片传给我
Give me a visual.
这是通风系统的过滤器
That's a filter for one of the ventilation systems.
你们有多少个这样的系统
How many systems do you have?
两个  一个在主医院内
Two, one in the main hospital,
另一个在基地的康复中心里
the other in the basement of the rehab center.
马上派人下去
I want men down there now!
B组  你们听到了吗
Bravo Team, are you getting this?
收到  我们走
Yeah. Roger that. Let's go.
好的
All right.
一  二  走  走
One, two. Go. Go.
喂  这里是禁区
Hey, guys. This is a restricted area.
能出示下证件吗
Can I see some I.D.?
先生
Sir.
稍等
Just a minute.
-马上  -稍等
- Now! - Just a minute!
-准备好回家了吗  大兵  -是的
- Ready to go home, solider? - Yeah.
再完成一件事
Just one more thing to do,
我们就送你上机
then we'll get you on that flight.
这是为了上飞机做准备的
A little something for the flight.
喂  就是你
Hey. Hey, you!
喂  我说
Hey. I said--
把她弄走
Get her off me!
关门  关门
Close the door, close the door!
所有人都不准离开
No one here is leaving!
把手拿出来
Show me your hands!
-手都拿出来  -举起手来
- Let me see some hands! - Hands up!
拦住他们  拦住他们
Keep them back. Keep them back.
总部  我们发现卡马里了
Zero, we got eyes on Kamali!
重复  卡马里在这
Repeat--we got Kamali here!
我们在基地里  准备离开
We are in the base. Prepare to exit.
我过去了
Coming to you!
上
Move!
各位  这里是禁区
Hey, fellas. This is a restricted area.
好了  阿迈  得手了  得手了
All right, Mikey. You got it, you got it.
该死  斯科特  我们来晚了
Shit! Scott, we're too late.
总部  卡马里已激活过滤器  下一步怎么做
Zero, Kamali's activated it. What do we do?
格雷中尉  关闭通风系统
Lieutenant Greg, shut the system down.
我做不到  长官  他们似乎做了某种干扰
I can't, sir. They seem to have jammed it somehow.
我已对医疗中心的通风系统做了隔离处理
I've managed to contain it in the medical center.
B组  马上出来
Bravo Team, get out now.
-该死的  -收到
- No shit! - Roger that.
按照安全禁闭步骤
Security lock down procedure!
回到各自单位中  行动  出发
Get to your units now! Let's go, let's go!
我佩枪武器都没带
Don't have a side arm or anything.
别担心这个
Don't worry about that.
安全禁闭  出发  出发
Security lock down. Let's go, let's go!
你们三个  保护飞机  我们得走了
You 3, secure the plane. We have to leave now.
我知道
I know.
病房已经被感染了
The ward's been infected.
-马丁内斯  -我没事
- Martinez. - I'm OK.
我知道结果的
I know the score.
只是汇报一下
I'm just reporting it in.
有人跟着我的话  就干掉他们
The men who were following me, kill them.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
五号机库存在可疑安全隐患
Possible security breach, hangar 5.
出发
Let's go!
走了
Go, go.
低头  低头  低头
Down, down, down!
他们在找维修队的人
They're looking for the maintenance guys.
到处都是20号分部的人
Section Twenty are everywhere.
-我们离开这儿  -好
- Let's get out of here. - All right.
-你占领了这架飞机吗  -是的
- Have you commandeered the plane? - Yeah.
-病毒在飞机上吗  -当然
- Is the virus on board? - Of course.
操
Fuck!
五号机库失去联络
We lost comms to hangar 5.
有监控录像吗
Do you have CCTV?
好的  往回倒一点
OK. Run it back.
那儿  暂停  放大
There. Hold the frame. Enhance it.
该死  长官  卡马里在这
Shit. Sir, Kamali's here,
两分钟前出现在五号机库
hangar 5, two minutes ago.
格雷中尉  带上人手立即赶过去
Lieutenant Greg, take some men and get down there with them now.
是  你们三个跟我走
Yes, sir. You 3 on me!
我跟他们一起去
I'm going with him.
B1  B2  汇报情况
Bravo One and Two, send sitrep.
总部  我们在康复中心外僵持不下
Zero, we're pinned down here outside the rehab center.
卡马里的人乔装成了宪兵
Kamali's men dressed as MPs.
结束战斗  赶去五号机库
Wrap it up and get to hangar 5.
卡马里在那
Kamali's there.
收到
Copy that.
进入五号机库
Entering hangar 5.
停  停车
Stop! Stop the car!
好吧  好吧  别开枪
All right, all right. Don't shoot, don't shoot.
反正你是不会想跟我们一起去的
You wouldn't want to come with us anyway, mate.
坐稳  我们上路了
Hold tight. We're on our way.
发现一个阵亡士兵
I've got a KIA.
我这里也有一个
I've got a man down.
停
Hold.
保持原位
Hold your position.
飞机上有动静
I see movement on the plane.
上前掩护
Moving to cover.
该死
Fuck!
我看到卡马里了
I've got eyes on Kamali.
他在飞机上
He's on the plane.
上面至少还有4个特务
There's at least 4 other clean skins.
我要上了
I'm going in.
B3  切勿靠近飞机  等待支援
Bravo 3, you stay off that plane and you wait for backup.
长官  我上了
Sir, I'm going in.
上
Move!
重复  等待支援
I repeat. Wait for backup.
B1  B2已经在路上了
Bravo One and Two are on their way.
瑞姆  不要上那架飞机
Richmond do not get on that plane.
朱莉娅
Julia.
B3  不要登机
Bravo 3, do not board that plane!
卡马里在哪
Where the fuck's Kamali?
改变计划
Change of plan!
在城市上空释放病毒
Disperse the virus over the city!
李奥  下面下些人
Leo, those people down there,
有女人  儿童和穆斯林
women, children, Muslims,
他们没有疫苗
they don't have the antivirus.
这叫战争的牺牲品  卡萨姆
Casualties of war, Qassem,
如同用来祭祀的羊羔
sacrificial lambs.
B3  这里是总部  收到回复
Bravo 3, this is Zero. Do you copy?
B3  收到回复
Bravo 3, do you copy?
我们是B1和B2
This is Bravo One and Bravo Two.
我们已经看见目标
We have target in sight.
重复  我们已看见目标
I repeat. We have eyes on the target.
B3  这里是总部  收到回复
Bravo 3, this is Zero. Do you copy?
朱莉娅  说话
Julia, come in!
卡马里在这  他在飞机上
Kamali's here. He's on the plane.
他们准备在柏林上空散播病毒
They're going to disperse the virus over Berlin.
我不能让那架飞机起飞
I can't let that plane take off.
你能不能给我的人一点时间
Will you just give my men some time?
-不行  -我的人还在飞机上
- Negative. - I've got a soldier on that plane!
你听到她说的话了
You heard what she said.
一旦成功起飞
If they get the wheels up,
他们会在城镇上空使用生化武器
they're gonna release the weapon over a populated area,
这绝不能发生
and I can't have that.
B1  B2  听到了吗
Bravo One and Two, you hear that?
阻止那辆飞机起飞
You stop that plane from taking off.
收到  我们去把那姑娘救下来
Copy that. Let's go get our girl back.
用地对空导弹锁定目标
I want surface to air missiles locked on.
已启动备用发射器
Back launcher online.
到这来
Come down here!
开近点
Get me close.
稳住
Keep it steady.
关闭坡道  关闭坡道
Close the ramp, close the ramp.
没有反应  坡道无法关闭
It's not responding. The ramp won't close.
加速起飞  听明白了吗
Speed the plane. Take off, you hear me?
二组  立即赶往三号跑道
Team two, get to runaway 3 now.
他们是你的人吗
Are they yours?
不是
Negative.
B组注意  六点方向有敌军靠近
Bravo, be advised, hostiles coming up on your 6.
-迈克  六点方向  -该死
- Mike, on our 6. - Shit!
操
Fuck!
交给我了
I got them!
前面的我来
I got front.
去你妈的
Fuck you!
换弹匣
Changing.
滚开
Fuck off!
搞定了?
Get him?
搞定了
We fucking got him.
干得漂亮  迈克尔
Nice, Michael, nice.
目标已锁定
长官  导弹已填装完毕
Missiles armed and ready, sir.
如果不在飞机上抓住卡马里  你永远也找不到抗病毒素
If we don't get Kamali off that plane, you may never find a cure,
那些被感染的人都死定了
and your infected people will not have a chance.
死750人总比死75万人强
750 is better than 750,000.
死了一个
One down.
我们去把那姑娘救回来吧
Let's get our girl back, huh?
注意  射击
Take it up, take it up.
该死
Oh, shit.
搞定他们  阿迈
Get them, Mikey.
朱丽娅  瑞姆  瑞姆
Julia? Richmond, Richmond!
-朱丽娅  你没事吧  -没事
- Julia, you all right? - Yeah.
听我命令
On my command.
等等
Wait.
卡马里在飞机上
Kamali's on board.
他们要击毁飞机
They're gonna shoot down the plane.
不  他有抗病毒素
No. There's a cure.
你们没时间了
You're out of time.
该死  我们得走了
Shit! We got to go, we got to go.
我们得离开这架飞机
We got to get off this plane.
准备
Stand by.
你等等不行吗
Will you wait?
他们可不是开玩笑
They're not kidding.
起落架已收起  发射
The wheels are up. Fire!
导弹已发射
B组  导弹已发射
Bravo, SAM incoming.
等等  我要做一件十分愚蠢的事
Hold on! I'm about to do something really fucking stupid!
九  八  七
9, 8, 7...
快撤  快
Let's Go! Do it!
五  四  三
5, 4, 3,
二  一
2, 1.
打击成功  目标已毁
Strike confirmed. Target destroyed.
该死的卡马里
Oh, shit. Kamali.
是个疯狂的[被烤焦的]恐怖分子
That's one toasted terrorist.
抗病毒素没了
The cure.
该死
Oh, fuck.
没有抓住卡马里  但我们救回了瑞姆
No Kamali, but we have Richmond.
收到  明白
Roger. Understood.
你做了正确的决定
You made the right call.
我也希望你的办法会奏效  [但风险太大]
I hope you're right.
爸爸  你还好吗
Hola, papi. ¿cómo estás?
不  我很好
No, no, no. Estoy bien.
我...
I-I...
我只是打电话问候几句
I was just calling to say hi.
我们的交易还算数吗
Is our deal still on?
卡马里死了
Kamali's dead.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我刚接了他的电话
I just got a call from him.
他不在飞机上
He wasn't on the plane.
如果你还想要他  半小时后中央广场见
If you still want him, center Square half an hour.
乌尔诺夫随时可能把车
Any minute now, Ulyanov's gonna pull up
停在广场的另一边
on the other side of that square.
他跟卡马里在一起  拿着最后一份病毒样本
He's with Kamali and the last of the virus.
我们是来这做交易的
We're here to do a trade.
拿什么交易
What are we trading?
拿我们俩交易是吧
It's us, isn't it?
我们是他唯一想要的东西
We're the only things he wants.
你一直等到现在才告诉我们?
And you waited till now to tell us?
说起来真他妈容易
How fucking convenient.
我要是早告诉你  你还会来这吗
Would you be here if I told you before?
好吧
All right.
在广场上做交易
So make a trade in a public square.
卡马里和病毒?
Kamali and the virus?
要是他在这释放病毒怎么办
What if he releases it?
我们这是按照乌尔诺夫的指示做
We're playing by Ulyanov's rules.
这是我们唯一的机会
It's our only chance.
去你的  我们刚从他手上逃出来
Fuck off! We just did a Houdini act to get away from that guy.
斯科特  只有卡马里知道抗病毒素在哪
Kamali's the only man who knows where the antivirus is, Scott.
没有药剂  马丁内斯以及基地里
Without a cure, Martinez and everyone at that base
所有被感染的人都得死
who's infected is dead,
如果隔离不彻底  天知道还会死多少人
and if we can't contain it there, who knows how many more?
"为了世界和平"这种屁话或许对他管用
That "Far, far better thing that I do" shit might work on him.
我可不吃你这套
Doesn't work on me.
那要怎么才能说服你  斯科特
So what will, Scott, what will?
"有点责任感?"
Sense of responsibility,
"不要自私地只考虑自己?"
a sense of giving a damn about something other than yourself?
皮拉戈娃会掩护你们的
Pirogova's got you covered.
只有她一个人?
But that's it?
要是惊动了乌尔诺夫  他肯定不会出现
We spook Ulyanov, he's gone,
卡马里也抓不到了
and Kamali with him.
听着  我不会命令你们这么做
Hey, listen. I won't order you to do this.
给我五分钟
Give me 5 minutes.
没问题
Sergeant.
我不能让你带着武器去  迈克尔
I can't send you over there armed, Michael.
你好
Hello?
我叫达米恩·斯科特...
My name's Damien Scott, and, uh...
有件事我得告诉你
I got--I got to tell you something.
我们怎么停车了
Why are we stopping?
公事
Business.
下车
Get out of the car.
艾斯特  一切都不会有事的
Ester, everything is going to be absolutely fine.
下车
Out of the car.
我们不会有事的
We're gonna be fine.
不  别走
No. Don't go.
-别担心  -下车
- Do not worry. - Get out of the car.
-别担心  -爸  别走
- Don't worry. - Dad, don't go!
不  不要
No! No! No!
-别搞我女儿  -闭嘴
- Not my daughter. - Shut up!
别搞我女儿  阿卡帝
Not my daughter. Arkady, not my daughter!
阿卡帝  请你不要伤害我女儿
Arkady, please do not hurt my daughter.
你本应该把杀害维克多的两个人交给我
You should have given me the two men who killed Viktor.
你当真相信
You really believe that
他们会来找你送死?
they're just gonna hand themselves over to you?
两个士兵换李奥·卡马里和病毒样本
Two soldiers for Leo Kamali and the virus?
有什么不好?
Why not?
洛克
Locke.
让他过来  带上病毒
Send him over with the virus.
好
Yes.
你要穿过广场
You're gonna cross that square.
她的小命在我手上
I will kill her.
怎么样
Cool?
我待会儿再告诉你
I'll tell you later.
我得走了
I have to go now.
爸  他们要拿你换迈克尔和达米恩
Dad, they're trading you in for Michael and Damien.
我说过  我不会伤害他们
I told you I wouldn't harm them.
但这个人会
But this man will!
那不是我能控制的  但你会平安的
That's out of my control now, but you will be safe.
走
Move.
记住  你妈妈爱你
Just remember that your mother loves you,
我也爱你
and I do, too.
快去
Move now.
我去了
I'm going.
你还觉得皮拉戈娃能射中?
You still think Pirogova can make the shot?
但愿如此
I fucking hope so.
你俩没有  那啥...
You guys didn't, uh...
有  一夜情嘛
Yeah. One-night thing.
她真他妈太疯狂了  连我都受不了
She's fucking crazy, even for me.
同志们  这可是公共频道
This is an open channel, guys.
不好意思
Sorry.
那瑞姆呢
What about Richmond?
我听着呢
Still open.
不好意思
Yeah, sorry.
有两个人在包抄我们  阿迈
Two guys packing either side of us, Mikey.
看到了
Yeah.
检查箱子
Check the case.
是空的  没有病毒
It's empty. There's no virus.
在他的手里
It's in his hand.
交易失败
There's no deal!
往前走  卡马里
Move, Kamali!
别动
Hold.
休想  交易失败了
No way! There's no trade!
该死  交易失败了
Shit! There's no deal!
把他们带过来  卡马里  快往前走
Bring them to me! Kamali, move! Move now!
交易失败了  交易无效
There's no deal! There's no trade.
B3  任意开火
Bravo 3, fire at will.
我现在就杀了她
I'll kill her right now!
爸爸  爸爸
Wh--Dad! Dad!
不  过来  过来
No! Come here, come here.
爸爸
Dad!
你不能过去
You can't go over there.
卡马里
Kamali.
看见他手里的东西了吗
You see that in his hand?
那是天花病毒
That's smallpox.
爸爸  求你
Dad, please!
那是生化武器
It's a biological weapon.
你不能过去
You can't go over there.
别这样  卡马里
Don't do it, Kamali.
你不能在这里释放病毒  这里不行
You're not gonna do this here, not here.
我别无选择
I have no other choice.
别犯傻  卡马里
Don't do it, Kamali.
她该怎么办
What about her?
你们都清楚  即使我现在交出病毒
You both know even if I hand this over now
我也见不到她了
I'm never gonna see her again.
你们会把我关在关塔纳摩那种鬼地方
You're gonna chain me up in some hole like Guantanamo,
这就是你们所谓的正义
your idea of justice.
爸爸  拜托放弃吧
Dad, please just give it up!
开枪
Take the shot.
不行长官  我们还没拿到抗病毒素
I can't, boss man. We haven't got the cure.
不要这样
Don't do it!
艾斯特  别动
Ester, don't, don't.
那你眼中的正义是什么  卡马里
And what's your idea of justice, huh, Kamali?
你在这个公共广场上释放病毒
You release this virus in this public square
造成成千上万无辜的人死亡
with thousands of innocent people?
这就是你所谓的正义吗
Is that your idea of justice?
无辜的人总是要死的
Innocent people always die.
那你的女儿呢  卡马里
Your own daughter, Kamali,
你的亲生女儿呢
your own fucking daughter?
看看她的脸
Look at her face.
好好看看
Look at her.
不要
No.
我不会为自己辩护
I won't justify myself to you.
你也许会理解我
You might understand,
可那又如何
and then where would you be?
杀了他
Kill him.
爸爸
Dad!
他妈的  不
Fuck! No!
爸爸
Dad!
抗病毒素在哪儿
Where's the cure?
药剂在哪儿  在哪儿
Where's the cure? Where is it?
迈克尔  你干了什么
Michael, what have you done?
只给正义之人
Only for the righteous.
爸爸  把药剂给他们好吗
Dad, give them the cure for me, yeah?
卡马里  药剂在哪儿
Kamali, where's the cure?
如果你需要给他们什么东西  就给他们吧
If there's something you need to give them, then do it, yeah?
为了我
Do it for me.
给他们吧  然后一切都会好起来的
Just do it, and then everything will be all right, OK?
拜托  卡马里  为了她
Come on, Kamali. Do it for her.
拜托  药剂在哪里
Just please. Where is it?
拜托你给他们好吗
Could you just please give it to them?
不只是我了我
Yeah. Don't just do it for me.
你也可以临死做个好人
You can die a good man.
你可以的  好吗
You can do this, OK?
好吗  拜托  告诉他们
All right? Come on. Just tell them.
告诉他们在哪
Tell them where it is.
卡马里  她是你生命中唯一真实的存在
Kamali, she's the one true thing in your life.
是你自己说的  为了她
You said so yourself. Do it for her.
拜托  告诉他们吧
Come on. Tell them.
项链  斯科特
It's the necklace, Scott.
在她的项链里
It's in her necklace!
给我  甜心  我拿走了
Give me that, sweetheart. Swetheart, give me that.
你做到了  他们知道了
You've done it. You've done it. You've told them.
现在  现在一切都好了
Now--now it can all be OK.
把这送去实验室
Get this to the lab.
爸爸
Dad?
爸  爸爸
Dad, Daddy.
爸爸  醒醒  爸爸  爸爸
Dad, wake up! Dad! Dad!
看来你终于报仇雪恨了
Looks like you got your man.
对  我现在可以安心睡觉了
Yeah. I'll sleep better now.
复仇是一种解放
Revenge is liberating.
你可以试试  菲利普
You should try it, Philip.
你有一支优秀的队伍
You got yourself a good team here.
如果你需要人手  随时联系我
If you ever need a hand, give me a call.
联邦安全局我是不会回去了
I'm done with FSB.
谢谢  妮娜
Thank you, Nina.
你父亲是个伟大的人
Your father was a great man.
他会为你感到骄傲的
He'd have been proud.
洛克要见你们
Locke wants you.
待会儿见
See you around.
当然
Yeah, sure.
借过
Sorry.
你今晚有安排吗
What are you doing tonight?
他八点以后都有空
Um, he'll be free from 8:00.
很好  我会联系你的
Good. I'll call you.
操  吓死哥了
Fuck. She is scary.
你还没领教过呢  兄弟
You have no idea, dude.
你得多喝几杯伏特加
You ought to take vodka
还有枪
and a gun.
同志们
Lads.
早  长官
Morning, boss.
我刚从实验室得知
I just heard from the lab.
抗病毒素的确在吊坠中
The antiviral was in the pendant.
马丁内斯和其他人会没事的
Martinez and the others are gonna be fine.
所以总体来看  你们干的不错
So all things considered, good job.
谢谢
Cheers.
奖章就省了  涨点薪水就行
Hold off on the medals. We'll just settle for a raise.
真的吗
Really?
我以为你们最不缺的就是钱
Thought that'd be the last thing you needed.
我刚刚在看贝鲁特行动的汇报文书
I was just going through the Beirut paperwork
你们有什么需要说明
if there's anything you'd like to claim
或是要上缴的吗
or hand in.
-没什么  -都写在里面了
- It's all good. - It's all there.
文件我先放在这了
I'll leave that with you, shall I?
他到底是怎么发现的
How the fuck did he work that out?
你会上缴的吧
You got to hand it to him, don't you?
糟了  我送给了一颗给一个姑娘
Fuck that. I handed one to a girl.
在哪送的
Oh. Where?
贝鲁特
Beirut...
那个的时候
at the time.
看来能带着价值25万美金钻石远走高飞的
The only one of us that's gonna get away with a $250,000 rock
只有那个乌克兰舞伎了
is a Ukrainian poll dancer.
不好意思  一点都不好笑
Sorry. That's not funny.
是不好笑
No.
不过这祸是你自己惹的
No, but it is your problem.
多谢
Thanks.
对  干的好
Yeah. Well done.
你他妈混帐
Fucking asshole.
欠你的啤酒
Fancy that beer?
还要我还吗
You want it?
好啊
Yes, I do.
什么鬼东西
What the fuck?
她不会传染吧
She's not, uh, contagious?
不会  没问题
No. You're safe.
滚出去
Get out of here.
我只是问问
I was just checking.
人家不想那啥嘛
I didn't want to, you know?
我以为你只要过了那道坎
You know, I thought if you pulled that stick out of your ass
你还值得我认真对待的
you'd be a guy I'd take more seriously,
不过看来这坎你是过不去了  不是吗
but it kind of belongs there, doesn't it?
我就当你是在夸我
I'll take that as a compliment.
我确实是在夸你
It was meant as one.
你们这些日子确实不好过
You boys had a pretty tough time.
火车上那些人呢
The guys on the train?
太迟了
We were too late.
看来我们比他们幸运多了
We had it easy here.
是的  没错
Yeah, you did.
你的口气越来越像洛克了
You're starting to sound more like Locke every day.
我当你这也是在夸我
I'm gonna take that as a compliment, as well.
这个真不是
It wasn't meant as one.
我对20号分部  以及你们的行事方式
You know, I had my doubts about Section Twenty
一直心存疑问
and how you guys do it,
不过和这些人在病房里待久了
but after being here with these guys in this room,
一切都明白了
it makes sense.
脏活总要有人做  你们是最合适的人选
Someone has to do it, and I can't think of anyone better.
你天生就是冲锋陷阵的料  对吧
This life's in your blood, isn't it?
是的
Yeah.
我们赢了
And we had a win.
你应该高兴点
You got to be happy about that, hmm?
赢了
A win.
我们赢了吗
Are we winning?
反正现在我觉得是赢了
I feel like I'm winning right now.
那个电话
So the, uh, the call.
对  电话
Yeah. The call.
我当爸爸了  迈克
I'm a dad, Mikey.
真的吗
Seriously?
没错
Yeah.
儿子还是女儿
Wow! Boy or girl.
儿子  名字叫芬恩
Boy. His name's Finn.
不错  多大了
All right. How old?
15岁
He's 15.
感觉如何
How's it feel?
挺好的
It feels good.
挺好
Yeah. Good.
对此我有些惭愧
Kind of ashamed of myself, you know?
你要去看他吗
Are you gonna see him?
嗯
Yeah.
我是想去
I want to.
我就知道应该自己留几颗钻石
Fucking knew we should have kept some of those diamonds.
我有孩子了
I got a kid.
没错  养孩子很贵的
Yeah, you do. Kids are expensive.
他会想要部好车
He's gonna want a fast car.
医疗费  牙医
Medical, dental.
他妈的  我还都没想到这些破事呢
Fuck. I didn't think of all that shit.
如果是你的儿子  说不定会有好几个女朋友
Yeah, and if it's your son, there might be a few girls.
那钻石就不够用了
Weren't enough diamonds for that.
看来我让洛克涨薪是说对了
It's good I asked Locke for a raise, huh?
这么说你要留在分部不走了?
So does that mean you're staying?
这是当然  好兄弟
Of course I am, buddy.
除此之外我还能干嘛
I'm not this good at anything else.
干这个你也不是特别在行
And you're not that good at this.